<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Categories on winnyace&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://winnyace.github.io/categories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Categories on winnyace&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://winnyace.github.io/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>osu! improvement week 6</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 10:51:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! This week is a bit disappointing due to serval reasons, but I think it&amp;rsquo;s time to do some retrospective and bring some news to this series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will present the scores, first off, in no chronological order. Spoiler alert: only 2 FCs this time. Most scores will be passes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First up is a score that I wanted since &lt;a href=&#34;../osu_i_w_3_4/&#34;&gt;week 3&amp;amp;4&lt;/a&gt;: Futari no Kimochi no Honto no Himitsu DT FC:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Qc8n4j_mCzk&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember that Flashlight score from &lt;a href=&#34;../osu_i_w_5/&#34;&gt;last week&lt;/a&gt;? Well, I got the FC!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DLnFqvxpeSk&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, problem is that I was lazy this week. I can&amp;rsquo;t lie to myself when I say that I didn&amp;rsquo;t play as much as I wanted to and for as long, so as a result, the rest of these scores will be passes that I got on maps that I feel are important. The first one to start is on &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/155288#osu/389703&#34;&gt;Insane Techniques&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/image1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image1&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sliders on this map fuck me up hard, not gonna lie, but it&amp;rsquo;s a fun map in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another fun map, or rather song, is &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/306028#osu/705091&#34;&gt;ENDLESS QUEER by Renard&lt;/a&gt;. The map is a screenjump fest. I enjoy it, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/image2.png&#34; alt=&#34;image2&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the mods side, I got this pass on &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/111760#osu/290581&#34;&gt;Diamond&lt;/a&gt; with HR. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping next week I will come with a FC on this since it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty average map.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/image3.png&#34; alt=&#34;image3&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back to NoMod, I got this almost FC on &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/104260#osu/274276&#34;&gt;Deep Sea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/image4.png&#34; alt=&#34;image4&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got a score on &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/145978#osu/620789&#34;&gt;FAKE PROMISE&lt;/a&gt; with HR and NF on, so does it count as a pass? I don&amp;rsquo;t know. I will put in away because I&amp;rsquo;m somewhat proud of it and it&amp;rsquo;s a banging song, not gonna lie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/image5.png&#34; alt=&#34;image5&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s about it, to be honest. Not really pleased with the output this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now for some news related to this series. On the 5th of September, I&amp;rsquo;ll start school, my last year of school. At the end of the year, I&amp;rsquo;m going to hold a very important exam here, the baccalaureate. This means that, next week, it is the last week of osu! improvement week, sadly. I&amp;rsquo;m not too sure what I will do this with this series, but I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of doing a monthly series instead. I will cover much more scores and I think it will be a better read than this weekly series. I want to keep playing osu! I don&amp;rsquo;t want to stop just now. It&amp;rsquo;s a fun game and it&amp;rsquo;s deeply fulfilling as well, and so I want to keep going and balance things out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still have one goal: FC &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/292077#osu/679779&#34;&gt;Asymmetry captin&amp;rsquo;s Extra&lt;/a&gt;. I said that I want to get this score I think in week 2 and it&amp;rsquo;s finally time. This last week it&amp;rsquo;s going to be Asymmetry time. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be like Azer getting his United score, or that&amp;rsquo;s the plan anyway. Speaking of United, I want that score as well, but I first want Asymmetry. I hope I will get it and if I won&amp;rsquo;t get it, well, shit happens and it&amp;rsquo;s fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to come back here next week with that score. See ya!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My configuration and stuff</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/configuration_and_stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:54:02 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/configuration_and_stuff/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few months ago, I put my configuration files in a GitHub repo, something I should have done as soon as I learnt how Git works, but alas. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you why things are the way they&amp;rsquo;re there and also I hope to give some opinions on some things related to configuration. Let&amp;rsquo;s begin!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I go into them, I want to get out some basic things out of the way. &lt;strong&gt;I use Arch Linux.&lt;/strong&gt; I know, first thing I say in this blog post related to my setup is my OS, Arch. I get it, but &lt;em&gt;why do I use Arch?&lt;/em&gt; Because my computer is sort of my center of activity. Let me explain: my uses for a computer are both to entertain myself, but also to work. I use my computer for practically everything I do on a day to day basis. I play games, I study here, I do quite a lot of things. You might think that Windows might be better at this job, because it has a wider support. The problem is that I dislike Windows and how things are done, so I&amp;rsquo;d rather deal with Linux than go through the nightmare that is Windows for me. I do have a Windows 10 install, but I barely use it and I use it mainly to play games hassle free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I&amp;rsquo;ve used a lot of different distributions of Linux over time, but the ones I&amp;rsquo;ve most experience with is Linux Mint and Manjaro. Mint was great back when I used Linux primarly for work. For a long time, my computer was very shit. It still isn&amp;rsquo;t the best, but it is certainly much better than before. Back then, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play games on Linux and if I did, it was Minecraft or emulated games, basically, really simple to run games on Linux, without much hassle. I didn&amp;rsquo;t knew a lot about Linux back then and I didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly care about the gaming side either. It&amp;rsquo;s why I had Windows installed, but with my new computer, I made the switch from Windows to Linux primarly. For the first few months, Mint was also great for gaming, but the problem was that some things with gaming on Linux require more special solutions. In my case, to run osu! without lots of crashes and without audio latency, I had to use special compiled Wine version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, Wine is a Windows translation layer for Linux. The easiest way explanation I&amp;rsquo;ve is that Wine simulates Windows in Linux. It translates what the program needs from Windows and points them to Linux appropiate things. It helps us run Windows apps in Linux. It&amp;rsquo;s great, only one problem: it&amp;rsquo;s kinda of a pain to use normally and installing Windows software to run on Linux isn&amp;rsquo;t always straight forward. There are solutions to this, from watching tutorials from people who did it manually, to automated installers and applications to help out people install and run their software, like Lutris, but even with these, things aren&amp;rsquo;t always straight forward and the installers are just scripts to run commands to the necessary things, managed and submitted by people like you and me, so if the maintainer of the installers disappears or doesn&amp;rsquo;t know any better way, well, you can probably see that things aren&amp;rsquo;t going to be well, which is what happened to me with osu!.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The solution to the problem at hand is using Lutris to install the game and then run the game using a special Wine version with the necessary patches, as well as changing your audio system, but that&amp;rsquo;s besides the point. All you need to know is that the Wine version required an esential package that was out of date on Mint and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the way to update the package to a newer version. The solution to that problem was to install Manjaro, by first ever distro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve a love hate relationship with Manjaro. It&amp;rsquo;s fine, I guess, for a beginner distro, but there are a lot of reasons why it&amp;rsquo;s not great, the biggest of which is that Manjaro holds back packages for 2 weeks before releasing them, which can cause a lot of issues with a system running rolling releases of packages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a bit of back and forth, I landed on Endeavour OS, which is actually the newbie friendly version of Arch. I like Endeavour and I recommended it over Manjaro for someone who wants to step it up a bit in terms of distros. After a few months, I decided to do the big step, mainly out of boredom, and just follow a guide for installing Arch and now, I&amp;rsquo;m running Arch. It&amp;rsquo;s great. I like it a lot, however, even if you use Mint or Ubuntu or something else, use it with bride, because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter in my eyes. &lt;strong&gt;Use whatever works for you, because it&amp;rsquo;s fine.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, another basic thing that I need to get out of the way: &lt;strong&gt;I use XFCE as my desktop environment.&lt;/strong&gt; Desktop environments are the big reason why I decided to stick with Linux through my first year or so of learning to use it. This freedom Linux opened up for me, a previous Windows only user, was mind-boggling to me. My enthusiasm for them died down over time as I realized my needs: I need a desktop environment that&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;decent looking and consistent theming, resource efficient, that works great without a window compositor and is simple enough for things to not break randomly.&lt;/strong&gt; After trying out GNOME, KDE Plasma, Cinnamon, XFCE and even went out of my way to get Openbox going, I decided that XFCE is the winner. It does everything I want it to do it: it&amp;rsquo;s decent looking, admittedly, not out of the box, but with a few simple changes, it can look pretty good, it&amp;rsquo;s resource efficent, especially compared to GNOME and Plasma, it works without a window compositor, unlike Cinnamon or GNOME, and it&amp;rsquo;s simple enough to cause me a headache like Plasma did. XFCE simply works for me. I love it. To make it look good, I use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/PapirusDevelopmentTeam/papirus-icon-theme&#34;&gt;Papirus Icon Theme&lt;/a&gt; with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nana-4/materia-theme&#34;&gt;Materia theme&lt;/a&gt; and the Ubuntu font as the system font. It looks great, in my opinion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think we&amp;rsquo;re done with the basic things. I should have probably called them &amp;ldquo;fundamental&amp;rdquo;, but whatever. Let&amp;rsquo;s go over what software I use on a day to day basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I use Firefox as my web browser.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Why?&lt;/em&gt; I just like it more than any offering and it works better in my experience than Vivaldi or any other Chromium based browser. I know Firefox fell down big time recently, but I don&amp;rsquo;t exactly have any problems with it, personally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I use either Neovim or Visual Studio Code to make the website posts.&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, I use code editors for that purpose. A little behind the scenes: since I made this blog in June, I made every post in LibreOffice, exported it to HTML and then went and fixed every issue that I saw. It didn&amp;rsquo;t take long, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really happy doing that all the time and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really happy with the theme I made. It&amp;rsquo;s based on Materia, but it looked wrong to me and phones didn&amp;rsquo;t play the website nicely either. A week or two ago, I was like &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;alright, let&amp;rsquo;s see what I can do&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; and I discovered Hugo. Hugo is a static web generator, exactly what I have, a static website. It promised a lot of easy abstraction compared to manually doing this, easy themes and, the best thing, is that I could write everything in Markdown file, which is fantastic. I could just use Neovim or VSCode, from beginning to end, with no issue, so I jumped in. I got things working, until I didn&amp;rsquo;t and I made a mess in the repo for this very website. I was lucky to back up the .git folder and the old website as well, otherwise, I would have been toasted. But now, I use VSCode now to write this. This is the first post I make &lt;em&gt;after&lt;/em&gt; the transition, which I hope enjoy as much as I do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://sw.kovidgoyal.net/kitty/&#34;&gt;kitty&lt;/a&gt; as my terminal.&lt;/strong&gt; Kitty? Yes. Kitty, the GPU based terminal emulator. &lt;em&gt;Why?&lt;/em&gt; Because of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sw.kovidgoyal.net/kitty/kittens_intro/&#34;&gt;kittens&lt;/a&gt; it has, more specifically, the icat kitten, which can display images in terminal. Now, I know you might ask &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;why do you want to display images in your terminal?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;. The reason, for me, is that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I use NNN or XFCE&amp;rsquo;s default file manager, Thunar, as my file manager.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jarun/nnn&#34;&gt;NNN&lt;/a&gt;, despite being the month with the funny challenge for the dudes out there, is a terminal, tiny, nearly 0-configuration file manager. It&amp;rsquo;s made in C, which makes it super fast as well, but it&amp;rsquo;s super powerful, especially with its plugin system. I&amp;rsquo;d like to make a more in-depth look into it and how I do my things, but for the moment, it&amp;rsquo;s my file manager of choice when in the terminal. I end up using Thunar much more, actually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, I want to make a tangent and talk a bit about what I will call &amp;ldquo;the dark side of Linux&amp;rdquo;. There are people who really like having everything ready, at their fingertips with their system. I like that too, but I&amp;rsquo;m clumsy and try to act fast when I can&amp;rsquo;t really. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure in this massive document I wrote so far, I will make a lot of typos, expressions that only I understand and other such things. It&amp;rsquo;s because I take things fast, when I really shouldn&amp;rsquo;t and I should take things slowly. Due to this, the &amp;ldquo;dark side&amp;rdquo; of Linux is not only dark, it&amp;rsquo;s something that I actively disagree with. What I refer by &amp;ldquo;the dark side&amp;rdquo; is software primarly controlled by the keyboard, through a terminal emulator. They offen require a lot of configuration, which isn&amp;rsquo;t a bad thing, after all I did make my own Openbox configuration from scratch, but the way that it is used, through the keyboard, just makes it extremely inefficient for me. I&amp;rsquo;m clumsy and I need things presented to me in a easy to disgest manner sometimes. NNN is an odd case for me, because I can use it fine, but there are a few things that I like doing on Thunar more than on NNN. I use both, but Thunar gets used a lot more than NNN due to this very reason. I feel like that&amp;rsquo;s how it goes for most people, actually, but I do feel somewhat held back sometimes due to being so clumsy with the keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, I&amp;rsquo;ll go to the Neovim configuration stuff. Depsite what I said above, I like Neovim sometimes. The vim controls are awesome for text. If you can handle them, you&amp;rsquo;re like a wizard. I love it, even though I&amp;rsquo;m not really a wizard with it. Either way, I&amp;rsquo;ve a bit to talk about there as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neovim is a fork, or another project based on something else, of Vim, which itself is a fork Vi. I don&amp;rsquo;t know the full details, but Vim and by extention Neovim are a bit lackluster when it comes to code editing out of the box. The solution are plugins that add functionality. I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/junegunn/vim-plug&#34;&gt;vim-plug&lt;/a&gt; for making that easier to handle. When it comes to plugins, the ones I like or use the most are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Yggdroot/indentLine&#34;&gt;indentLine&lt;/a&gt;: adds a little indentation line for easier readability;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/junegunn/fzf.vim&#34;&gt;fzf.vim&lt;/a&gt;: nice little file finder for vim based on fzf;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mg979/vim-visual-multi&#34;&gt;vim-visual-multi&lt;/a&gt;: adds multicursor support;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mcchrish/nnn.vim&#34;&gt;nnn.vim&lt;/a&gt;: uses nnn as a file picker in vim;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/neoclide/coc.nvim&#34;&gt;coc.nvim&lt;/a&gt;: general purpose extension host and language server host, basically adding lanaguge specific support in vim, among other things;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tpope/vim-fugitive&#34;&gt;vim-fugitive&lt;/a&gt;: adds Git support to vim;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vimlab/split-term.vim&#34;&gt;split-term&lt;/a&gt;: adding more functionality to the terminal command in neovim.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, I went through what I wanted to talk about. Other software I use for making things together here is OBS, for capturing the gameplay footage in my osu! improvement posts, and Kdenlive, the video editor I use to make them seem nicer after I capture my footage.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>osu! improvement week 5</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:54:50 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! I kinda missed the mark, not gonna lie. I want from now on to post these weekly updates on Sunday. This week is missed, but next one, it will be from today to Sunday next week. I’ll try to keep my promise. Anyway, with that aside, this week was another mostly lazy one, but I got some pretty good scores. Let’s begin!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After my post from last week, I didn’t play until Thursday. That isn’t very good, but yeah… I started to play on Wednesday and I got two scores that I’m quite proud of. The first one is a slightly weird jump map, &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/962568#osu/2015483&#34;&gt;Futari Dake no Kotoba&lt;/a&gt;. I’m not sure if these jumps are called anti-jumps or not, but I think they’re.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/L61ITNUTb60&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second score is done on a more traditional map. I’m not sure if it is something very notable, though, so I’ll just put the score screenshot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/17aug2022.png&#34; alt=&#34;image1&#34;&gt;
Pardon the 4:3 resolution. how I play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next day, I got another score, on &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/710329#osu/1502636&#34;&gt;Burnt Rice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jvyaAno1IHA&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, I was away from home the whole day, and so I couldn’t play, but then on Sunday, I got a pretty nice score that I wanted for some time, &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/408558#osu/887145&#34;&gt;Koitsubakihime&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TnjgvvwSy8A&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The accuracy could have been much better, if you ask me, but it’s still something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides that, I’ve decided on a new goal: FC &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/909559#osu/1897995&#34;&gt;Starting Forest by 3R2, the Insane difficulty&lt;/a&gt; with Flashlight. Yeah, Flashlight. I like Flashlight. If there is a mod that I dislike, it is Hidden, not only because I can’t play it, but because it is a very easy to spam. The amount of difficulty Hidden adds is negligible most of the time. It depends the map as well, but it depends a lot more on how familiar you’re with the mod. With a little practice, you can become just as good with HD as with NoMod. Now, Flashlight… Flashlight is also a visual mod, like Hidden, but with Flashlight, you’ve to be familiar with the map, rather than the mod. It’s a mod that challenges you to remember patterns and execute them with little visual clue and I find that very intriguing, which is why I want to get this score with Flashlight. I got some other Flashlight scores in the past, but this is the first one that passes 4 stars in difficulty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That Sunday, things were going pretty well with attempts andlearning the map. It’s quite an easy to retry spam the map due toits length, which is what I did for the most part that day. I also tried to split the map in parts to learn it, but I quickly dropped that approach  when I realize that, with Flashlight, the area around the cursor slowly shrinking with combo. This is the best score on the map that I got with Flashlight that day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/XFFjkCGCNfs&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, I continued my attempts and also played some other maps and I got two nice scores. The first one is on &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/219380#osu/555965&#34;&gt;Toumei Elegy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/awc7F38-wl0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last score of that day was on &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/220694#osu/516452&#34;&gt;Ageage Again&lt;/a&gt;, with Hard Rock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/KbIAu6bi9O4&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll talk more about my progress with the Flashlight score in the next week&amp;rsquo;s post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And with that, we reach today, late and overdue with this blog post… I’m sorry. I will try my best next week to post here on Sunday. I’ve a new blog post in the meantime coming up, hopefully this week, so stay tuned. See ya!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>osu! improvement week 3 and 4</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_3_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 13:59:27 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_3_4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Towards the beginning of week 3, I got sick and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really play, which made me feel like these two weeks would be boring, but I got some pretty good scores overall, and I think I&amp;rsquo;m starting to go down the right path. let&amp;rsquo;s begin with week 3. the only score worth noting here is a FC on an, at the time, newly ranked map of a Gochiusa song. it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty bog standard map, but getting it was very rewarding. below you&amp;rsquo;ve the score.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/@winnyace:e/Shinsaku-no-Shiawase-wa-Kochira!-Cappucino-FC:1?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That happened on the 29th of July. Afterwards, nothing really happened. a bad thing I do a lot is giving up on a map after a mistake. that&amp;rsquo;s something that hurts me, a lot, especially mentally. this game is very mental, I feel like. a lot of what I&amp;rsquo;m doing most of the time is fighting myself to keep going and finish the map. always finish the map&amp;hellip; always. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get anything done in that weekend. only thing I got was a new goal: FC &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/1567488#osu/&#34;&gt;Colorful by L1gHT_u&lt;/a&gt;. I got a pretty big combo on it already and I felt I could do it, but I got nothing going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/8aug20221.png&#34; alt=&#34;image1&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Monday, I made the previous blog post and played more Colorful. I still got nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Colorful.-%28Asterisk-DnB-Remix%29-Reunion./0a897485feec80e2fa20437290d2bedc6b0de729?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then on Tuesday, I began playing. It felt like yet another boring slog of a day with more Colorful attempts, until I began playing DT on the ED or OP, I don&amp;rsquo;t really know for sure to be honest, for the Kill me baby anime, at least I think that&amp;rsquo;s the name. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know, all I know is that the song is jamming hard. I began putting some plays into it, going to the end and then&amp;hellip; it happened&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Futari-no-Kimochi-no-Honto-no-Himitsu-Insane-almost-FC/465329915dfeec6bbbd9293cac365396ae0e0602?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;almost&amp;hellip; Yeah&amp;hellip; it was pretty heart breaking. I tried putting another play in, but my electricity cut off and I lost interest by the time it got back on. I knew that I could do it, though, so that became another goal.
For the next few days, nothing happened. I played until I got bored or annoyed, left the game and then went and did something else. That&amp;rsquo;s another problem I feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve: I can&amp;rsquo;t exactly focus on something for a very long period. around the one hour mark is when I get extremely bored and I&amp;rsquo;ve to do something else. I wonder if being constantly online for the past&amp;hellip; almost 10 years at this point, perhaps even more, finally starts getting to me and makes have a lower attention span. I mean, it could be worse. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a TikTok account, but I heard that app reduces attention span at an incredible rate, alongside other nasty side-effects. Admittedly, social media in general does that. I wonder if people actually sit here and read this. If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this: hi, I guess! Anyway, tangent aside, another problem I feel I&amp;rsquo;ve is that I get annoyed, very quickly. I think I said this before in previous post, but I have high expectations of myself when playing, which is quite bad for my mental health, my performance and my equipment as well. I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you how many monitor punches I did when missed that DT score. It&amp;rsquo;s not good going berserk over a game, even if you care a lot about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that DT score, nothing happened. I was thinking to myself what I will show here. I was just playing new things, because I could get anything going in terms of goals, at all. On Friday, however, things took a great turn. The day itself was quite horrible, actually. It was one of those days where you just feel bad and horrible. I felt like even if I don&amp;rsquo;t get anything, I&amp;rsquo;d log in to just have some fun clicking some circles. I had no expectations, at all. And so, I got one of my best days, score wise, in my recent memory It started on a pretty simple map&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Jinsei-Matatabi-Expert-FC/e2f85fb47d26033ff79dd0eb75fdf757efc2b137?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided then to just play and I landed on Asymmetry, and I began playing&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Asymmetry-captin%27s-Extra--pass-2/cf14b2f38a1e9f3647f9177b8423ba7299f64103?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wasn&amp;rsquo;t a FC, but I&amp;rsquo;m getting closer to it. I took it happily and gratefully. I continued playing, now in a good mood. Nothing really happened until I decided to play Colorful again, with no expectation whatsoever&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Colorful-%28Asterisk-DnB-Remix%29--Reunion-FC/52a964a1d2dc2cfb8786935c6c08173fa6251a6e?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To say that this didn&amp;rsquo;t put me in a good mood would be a lie. It made me extremely happy. I played for a bit longer, but I got bored, not gonna lie. It was a fun day that Friday, at the end.
The next day, Saturday, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play at all, which is bad. I was still riding on that happy wave that I got from my FC on Colorful. I might have been able to get a FC on Asymmetry, but alas, it&amp;rsquo;s fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, so yesterday, it was a pretty slow day, but I manage to get a HR score. The accuracy is pretty meh, but I think the score is overall pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Polygon-Asphyxia%27s-Insane-/bc2ffcd3df3550c19745c1f50f25257f9c9146d1?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, these weeks were fine to good, actually. I&amp;rsquo;m really happy I decided to make the two weeks lumped together, because it gave me more time to get some good stuff going. I&amp;rsquo;m not going to do the same with week 5, though, unless something horrible happens, so see ya next week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>osu! improvement week 3 delay</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_3_delay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 13:55:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_3_delay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi. Due to me getting slightly sick and also not enough scores to show, I decided to not do this week and I&amp;rsquo;ll lump week 3 and 4 into one. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for the inconvenience and I hope that I&amp;rsquo;ll show some good stuff next week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>osu! improvement week 2</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 13:59:27 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! This is the second week of my osu! improvement journey some nice things have happened, but it&amp;rsquo;s yet another, sort of, lazy week. Let&amp;rsquo;s begin!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Monday and Tuesday, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play at all. no excuse, really. Just laziness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, I played for the first time this week. it was pretty good day I got two HR scores.  Admittedly, they&amp;rsquo;re quite  boring scores, but I think it&amp;rsquo;s a step in the right direction when it comes to HR.  both are done on &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/748836#osu/1577478&#34;&gt;Best FriendS by sahuang.&lt;/a&gt; What can I say? I like the song :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Best-FriendS-N-a-s-y-a%27s-Insane--%2BHR/8a5bd31f314b24076b2d13cede3a9cf97fb7650b?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the first replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Best-FriendS-Everlasting-Memories--%2BHR/7737f640a86e66b726a7b8dd8368441e988be3ca?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the second replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also played a tech, I guess I can call it, map. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty fine score, I think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/25jul20221.png&#34; alt=&#34;image1&#34;&gt;
I also got a score on a Non Non Biyori DNB Remix. It&amp;rsquo;s a 54 seconds map, but has CS6 and it&amp;rsquo;s a stream map. I&amp;rsquo;ll take that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/25jul20222.png&#34; alt=&#34;image2&#34;&gt;
I&amp;rsquo;ve also played a bit of DT on Hidamari Days. Below you&amp;rsquo;ve the score in video form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Hidamari-Days-DT/13d54fe68d3bab94edac8d628c7d47c4506e7adc?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admittedly, these scores aren&amp;rsquo;t something impressive, but I believe it&amp;rsquo;s the step towards the right direction. by this time, I still haven&amp;rsquo;t set a specific goal, however, that changed quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play yet again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Friday, I played for a bit. Nothing much, however. I got a NoMod FC on Rave 2 Rave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/25jul20223.png&#34; alt=&#34;image3&#34;&gt;
This song is jamming! Not my score, though. My accuracy is quite bad, not gonna lie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday is when I finally got a goal: &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/292077#osu/679779&#34;&gt;FC Asymmetry by Gaia, captin&amp;rsquo;s Extra difficulty.&lt;/a&gt; The map is pretty bog standard these days, I believe, but it&amp;rsquo;s a 6 star map, the song is pretty good, in my opinion, and I think I can get the FC. below you&amp;rsquo;ve the attempt I&amp;rsquo;ve done on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/$/embed/Asymmetry-captin%27s-Extra--pass/c11bbdd290fbd9aef9726bca4b7c36000bbb7213?r=42PNMr5RuN12RUSUC17dRvdcy8EYov9h&#34;&gt;Click here for the replay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You probably saw that I&amp;rsquo;ve a 1000+ combo score on this already.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/25jul20224.png&#34; alt=&#34;image4&#34;&gt;
I set that score at beginning of this month. I&amp;rsquo;ve missed at the end, due to the pressure of that FC. This is something I will need to deal with. I panic when I&amp;rsquo;m close to getting a FC. I think everybody does, actually, but some keep their focus and pull through. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll try to regulate my breathing when I&amp;rsquo;m close to getting the FC. I think that&amp;rsquo;s the best solution. Trying to hyperfocus on the map will only result in bad things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ends this week. I kinda want to play osu! right now, believe it or not. See ya next week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>osu! improvement week 1</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 18:35:53 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week was mostly about getting started with this and trying to enter into a routine. I wanted to play around the same time every single day, but there are a few challenges to that. back in 2020, I used to play around 10-11AM in the morning, for a hour or two, almost every single day. considering I&amp;rsquo;ve other things on my plate nowadays, though, I can&amp;rsquo;t exactly do that, but I think skipping a day or two won&amp;rsquo;t be the end of the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;another thing I tried to do is to try to keep playing even on a bad day. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent this week mostly derusting and trying to force myself to keep going, no matter what. I believe this is the true challenge of improvement at anything: the mindset you&amp;rsquo;ve towards it. if you want results from the get go, you&amp;rsquo;ll fail to meet them. this happens to me, all the time. I&amp;rsquo;ve very high expectations of myself and I&amp;rsquo;m too impatient with myself as well. real improvement takes time, sometimes a lot of time, and a lot of effort as well  and we can easilyblock progress by being so judgmental over our own performance.  this is something that will take me some time, I believe. it&amp;rsquo;s just something I&amp;rsquo;ve to accept: it will take time to see results. I plan that on bad days to try and play things that I know I can&amp;rsquo;t really play exclusively. since I can&amp;rsquo;t really play such maps, I don&amp;rsquo;t have high expectations of me to do well, so I can impress myself without a ton of work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for the moment, I don&amp;rsquo;t have very specific goals, but I should get very soon. a problem I&amp;rsquo;ve with goals, however, is how unrealistic I make them. I said once to myself that if I put in the effort to FC &lt;a href=&#34;https://osu.ppy.sh/beatmapsets/536872/#osu/1142960%22&#34;&gt;oddloop&lt;/a&gt; I can do it. well, yes, that&amp;rsquo;s true, but it&amp;rsquo;s a very difficult map for me currently, especially the ending. the map requires a lot of precise aim, something I&amp;rsquo;m currently trying to get back and continue working on, as well as reading. my goals have to be something I can reasonably do. I&amp;rsquo;ll see what will be able to come up with and I will share them here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be honest: I didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly put much effort this week into this. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to figure out how to make this as well. I think I will take notes during the play session, so for each day there&amp;rsquo;s something more concrete,  not just this vagueness I did this week. I also want to post the scores I believe to be good to great as well and maybe try to narrate these little blogs and make a little video each week for them. I will think about it. if you&amp;rsquo;ve an idea or you just want to give me feedback, you can always find my contact information on this blog. I&amp;rsquo;m most active on Discord.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s for the moment. thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>osu! improvement week 0</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:28:33 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/osu_i_w_0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A big part of my teenage life was discovering and playing osu!, a pretty popular rhythm game. I’ve been playing since June of 2016 and ever since then, I wanted to be a good player. Due to laziness, lack of motivation and other similar things, in my 6 years of playing this game, I didn’t get extremely far, but I keep on trying to both improve and have fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the summer of 2020, I was playing this game quite a lot, to the point where I was doing things that were previously impossible for me. I felt really good about that time and I want to redo it and also document the entire process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the title suggests, I&amp;rsquo;m going to do these weekly, ideally. I will talk about the scores I have set in that week, some stuff outside the game but still related somewhat, My thoughts on different things, and other things that I find important to share. My main goal with this week series is start doing those amazing things again, while also sharing on some of my knowledge that I have gained and I will gain with this. I hope it will be fun. If you guys have suggestions, here&amp;rsquo;s my contact information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s to some great circle clicking! ^o^&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nostalgia</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/nostalgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 14:29:02 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/nostalgia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was at my computer, like I always am. Just finished my cycling session and I was really bored, and I saw a Vtuber meme which had a low quality version of Candyland by Tobu, released by NCS, I think(?). Out of my boredom, I decided to actually search for the meme. I’ve enjoyed for the… 10 seconds that it is funny, and then, out of nowhere, I got the title of a song from my childhood in my head: Imaginary Friends by Laszlo, also released by NCS. I suppose, I should explain a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For as long as I can remember, I’ve watched YouTube videos. It is, by far, my most visited website on the Internet and represents a huge majority of the content I watch regularly, even today. When I was small, around 10-11, years old, I was extremely into Minecraft and during that era, a lot of what the youtubers I’ve watched were doing Minecraft videos and more specifically Minecraft PVP. And a lot of them used songs from NCS. I remember one youtuber who used that song in the background for one of his survival games series. It was a really beautiful moment when I finally found that song.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And with little song, I remembered a lot of things of my childhood&amp;hellip; I’m certainly not 60 years old or anything, but it is still nostalgic for me to remember a time when I was more youthful and innocent. I used to add random people on Skype, yeah Skype, and play Minecraft with them. I used to use a CRT monitor. I used to have a Pentinum 4. I used to make videos on that poor Pentinum 4! Yeah, haha! &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/c/KillerGamingOldschoolGaming&#34;&gt;Search DerFlash on YouTube&lt;/a&gt; (it’s in Romanian, but still) and you will find my old attempts at making videos. It is hilariously cringey and corny but man, I was actually trying things back then. That’s something I can’t do it easily. Man… what a time was back then. It’s a time now too, don’t get me wrong, but it’s more weird now… perhaps I’m just more self-aware of my own being than I used to. I certainly need to be more like a kid and just try things, for the sake of trying them. Perhaps that will help me grow as an individual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve quite a bit of embarrassing stuff to talk about my past, but that’s for another time, I think.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World</title>
      <link>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:21:04 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winnyace.github.io/posts/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, world!
I&amp;rsquo;m currently still trying to put everything together for the blog and website. right now, for some reason, the new style isn&amp;rsquo;t being implemented, which is kind of annoying. I had to delete my previous repo for this to work, sadly. it&amp;rsquo;s fine now, though. I&amp;rsquo;m glad how well this turned up to be. now, for the future. I&amp;rsquo;m not too sure what I will do here, but I know I want to do something and hopefully share on my little bit of knowledge I&amp;rsquo;ve and leave my mark on this world, somehow. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably talk about&amp;hellip; whatever goes through my mind at a current time about a topic, really. we&amp;rsquo;ll see. for the time being, though, hello world!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
