<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rambles on winnyace&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>http:/winnyace.github.io/tags/rambles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rambles on winnyace&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.144.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:22:19 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http:/winnyace.github.io/tags/rambles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rambling a bit about my own motivation</title>
      <link>http:/winnyace.github.io/posts/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:22:19 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http:/winnyace.github.io/posts/motivation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! Long time no see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever struggled with motivation? Because I do, all the time. It is a pain in the butt. Especially when you&amp;rsquo;re bored and you wonder what you could do to not be bored, like me right now, or when you have an important exam coming up and you just can&amp;rsquo;t be arsed to do anything for it. This is the situation I am in right now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rambles: Long time no see.</title>
      <link>http:/winnyace.github.io/posts/talking_time_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:12:42 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http:/winnyace.github.io/posts/talking_time_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yo! Long time no see. I have began university, at computer science. Things have been mixed, but mostly well. I kinda just want to do a post to say that I&amp;rsquo;m here and I want to do stuff here. Not sure what, but I know want to do stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanna try to do blog posts that talk about random stuff, either in my life or online that I have an interest in and that sparked my own curiosity. I wanna try to bring back the osu! improvement week thing, but that will happen in the summer. I even want to try and begin making videos and stuff, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know how that would work. There are a lot of things that I wanna do, but I can&amp;rsquo;t lie when I say that I am scared to do them. I make this blog post part because I wanted to do so for some time, but also because this week has been &lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt; difficult for me. I have some things to say and hopefully learn from, but I will try to take them one at a time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nostalgia</title>
      <link>http:/winnyace.github.io/posts/nostalgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 14:29:02 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http:/winnyace.github.io/posts/nostalgia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was at my computer, like I always am. Just finished my cycling session and I was really bored, and I saw a Vtuber meme which had a low quality version of Candyland by Tobu, released by NCS, I think(?). Out of my boredom, I decided to actually search for the meme. I’ve enjoyed for the… 10 seconds that it is funny, and then, out of nowhere, I got the title of a song from my childhood in my head: Imaginary Friends by Laszlo, also released by NCS. I suppose, I should explain a bit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
